Finding Aid for Commencement week programs
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Commencement week programs 1887-1947, 1904-1928
University of Michigan.
1 linear feet (in 3 boxes.)
FImu E3 C734w
Programs for University of Michigan commencement week activities, issued for each school and college, and usually have embossed limp leather covers.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was assembled from a variety of sources.
No further additions to the collection are expected. Occasionally a new program is received.
The record group is open to research.
These beautiful leather-bound programs describe the scheduled activities of Commencement Week. They also list the graduating seniors, class officers, and occasionally faculty members. Sometimes there are prints, drawings, or photographs of campus buildings, scenes, or perhaps the dean of the school. They are arranged alphabetically by the name of the school and thereunder chronologically.
Subjects:
University of Michigan--Commencements.
- Business Administration
  - 1926 (Box 1)
  - 1927
- Dentistry
  - 1887 (Box 1)
  - 1900
  - 1909
  - 1913
  - 1914
  - 1915, 2 copies
  - 1918
  - 1919
- Education
  - 1924 (Box 1)
  - 1925
  - 1928, 2 copies
  - 1929
- Engineering, 2 folders
  - 1902 (Box 1)
  - 1904
  - 1906
  - 1907
  - 1908
  - 1909
  - 1910
  - 1911
  - 1912
  - 1913
  - 1915
  - 1916
  - 1917
  - 1919
  - 1920
  - 1921
  - 1923
  - 1924
  - 1926
  - 1928
  - 1929
- Homeopathic Medicine and Surgery
  - 1908 (Box 1)
  - 1919
- Law, 2 folders
  - 1894, 3 copies (Box 1)
  - 1904
  - 1906
  - 1907
  - 1908
  - 1909
  - 1910, 2 copies
  - 1912
  - 1914
  - 1916
  - 1917
  - 1922
  - 1925
  - 1926
  - 1927
  - 1930
  - 1931
  - 1932
  - 1941
- Literary, 5 folders
  - 1894 (Box 2)
  - 1902
  - 1904
  - 1905
  - 1906
  - 1907
  - 1908, 2 copies
  - 1909
  - 1910
  - 1911
  - 1912, 2 copies
  - 1913
  - 1914
  - 1915
  - 1916
  - 1917
  - 1918
  - 1919
  - 1920
  - 1921, 2 copies
  - 1922
  - 1923
  - 1924
  - 1925
  - 1926
  - 1927, 2 copies
  - 1928
  - 1929
  - 1930, 2 copies
  - 1931
  - 1932
  - 1936
- Medicine and Surgery
  - 1888 (Box 3)
  - 1889
  - 1904
  - 1906
  - 1907
  - 1908
  - 1909
  - 1910
  - 1915
  - 1916
  - 1918
  - 1920
  - 1924
  - 1925
  - 1926
- Pharmacy
  - 1908 (Box 3)
  - 1909
  - 1910
  - 1912
  - 1913
  - 1918
  - 1927
  - 1928
- Senior Class
  - 1933 (Box 3)
  - 1934
  - 1935
  - 1936
  - 1937, 3 copies
  - 1939
  - 1942
  - 1947
  - 1949, 2 copies
  - 1956
Related Material
Additional commencement week programs (plain printed, without leather covers) can be found Chief Marshall (University of Michigan) records.